Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art financial records, 1872-1988 COR0004.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Investment and Real Estate records, 1869-1979; Series 6
  - Real Estate Notes, 1869-1979; Series 6 Subseries 3
    - Wood, Waddy B.: 17th St. Property-Possible Purchase, 1938; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Wood, Waddy B.: 17th St. Property-Possible Purchase, 1938; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans, A-Z, 1938; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Board of Temperance, Prohibition & Public Morals (Mortgage), 1939; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Cahill, James A.: Note Held on Lot 4, Square 2522, 1939; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Crandall, Paul: Corner Lot-Oak & Brown Streets, 1939; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Miller, Wm. C. & Allison N.: Various Properties, 1939; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Parkhurst, Frederic & Abby: "Edgemoor" Estate-Foreclosure, 1939; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Parkhurst "Edgemoor" Estate-Foreclosure Cont'd, 1939; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Parkhurst "Edgemoor" Estate-Foreclosure-Correspondence, 1939; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Parkhurst "Edgemoor" Estate-Foreclosure-Correspondence, 1939; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Parkhurst "Edgemoor" Estate-Foreclosure-Correspondence, 1939; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - 17th St. Property-Possible Sale, 1939; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Service Parking Corp.: 17th St. Property (Rental), 1939; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Spigel, Ben: 1380 Fort Drive (Mortgage), 1939; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Wolcott, Marthena: 4655 Garfield St. (Mortgage), 1939; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans, A-Z, 1939; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Misc. Real Estate Records, 1939; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Central Building Company-Building Loan, 1940; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Donahue, Dr. Matthew E.: 4826 Conduit Rd. (Mortgage), 1940; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Horn, Betsy B.: 1525 14th St. (Mortgage), 1940; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Parkhurst "Edgemoor" Estate-Foreclosure-Correspondence, 1940; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Parkhurst "Edgemoor" Estate-Foreclosure-Correspondence, 1941; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Scheele, Clifton & Russell: Building Loan-J.C. Penney (in Clarendon), 1940; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - 17th St. Property-Possible Sale, 1940; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Service Parking Corp.: 17th St. Property (Rental), 1940; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans, A-Z, 1940; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Kelly, Paul C.-3349 Runnymede Place (Mortgage), 1941; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Miller, Wm. C. & Allison N.: 3010 45th St. (Mortgage), 1941; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Parkhurst "Edgemoor" Estate-Sale to Longfellow School, 1941; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Parkhurst 'Edgemoor" Estate-Sale to Longfellow School, 1941; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Protestant Episcopal Cathedral Foundation-CGA Purchase of its Notes to Reduce Cathedral Debt, 1941; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Scheele, Clifton & Russell: Building Loan for J.C. Penney, 1941; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - 17th St. Property-Sale to U.S. Government, 1941; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans A-Z, 1941; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Brunthauer, Elizabeth-503 12th St. (Mortgage), 1941; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Foster, Chas.-3805 17th St. (Mortgage), 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Hadley, Agnes M.-4304 Forest Lane (Mortgage), 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Johnson. Geo. H.: 431 Oglethorpe St. (Mortgage), 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Kelly, Paul C.-3349 Runnymede Place, 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Miller, Wm. C. & Allison N.-Various Properties, 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - O'Neal, Nelson B.: 3011 Albemarle St. (Mortgage), 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Parkhurst: "Edgemoor" Estate-Sale to Longfellow School, 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Protestant Episcopal Cathedral Foundation-Registered Notes, 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Reynolds, Jos.-1700 Allison St. (Mortgage), 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Scheele, Clifton & Russell-Building Loan for J.C. Penney, 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Schreech, Geo. & Elma-5931 31st Place (Mortgage), 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Schwatz, Albert-923 Lewis Ave. (Rockcrest, MD), 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - 17th St. Property-Sale to U.S. Government, 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Service Parking Corp.-17th Street Property-Settlement of Rental, 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Snyder, Merle B.-4700 Langorum Lane (Chevy Chase, MD), 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Spigel, Ben: 1380 Fort Drive (Mortgage), 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Thompson, Catherine B.-159 Quincy St. (Chevy Chase, MD), 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Wolf, Gertrude-2331-2333 Green St. (Mortgage), 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans A-Z, 1942; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Atherton, Leland-28 Dalecarlia Dri. (Westmoreland Hills, MD), 1943; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Bingham, Bianca-313 Rosemary St. (Chevy Chase, MD), 1943; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Board of Temperance, Prohibition & Public Morals (Mortgage), 1943; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Brooks, Thos. R.-3927 Oliver St. (Chevy Chase, MD), 1943; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - Horn, Betsy B.: 1525 14th St. (Mortgage), 1943; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - Leitch, Pauline-4812 43rd Pl. (Mortgage), 1943; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - O'Neal, Nelson B.: 3011 Albemarle (Mortgage), 1943; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - Protestant Episcopal Cathedral Foundation-Notes, 1943; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - Scheele, Clifton & Russell-Building Loan-J.C. Penney, 1943; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - Silber, Irving-4925 4th St. (Mortgage), 1943; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 87)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans A-Z, 1943; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - Cox, Dorothy M.-5754 Colorado Ave. (Mortgage), 1944; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - Protestant Episcopal Cathedral Foundation-Registered Notes, 1944; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 90)
    - Robbins, Rainard B.-Trust, 1944; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Scheele, Clifton & Russell-Building Loan-J.C. Penney, 1944; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - Sebring, Frank W.-3349 Runnymede Pl. (Mortgage), 1944; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans A-Z, 1944; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 94)
    - Miller, Wm. C. & Allison N.-Various Properties, 1945; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - Parkhurst Property-Longfellow School, 1945; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 96)
    - Protestant Episcopal Cathedral Foundation-Notes, 1945; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 97)
    - Robbins, Rainard-5308 Moorland Ave. (Edgemoor, MD), 1945; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 98)
    - Scheele, Clifton & Russell-Building Loan, 1945; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 99)
    - Wolf, Gertrude-2331-2333 Green St. (Mortgage), 1945; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 100)
    - Misc Mortgage Loans, 1945; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 101)
    - Auldridge, Francis-25 W. Everett St. (Chevy Chase, MD), 1946; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 102)
    - Brooks, Thos. R.-3927 Oliver St., 1946; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 103)
    - Leitch, Pauline-4812 43rd Pl., 1946; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 104)
    - Protestant Episcopal Cathedral Foundation-Notes, 1946; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 105)
    - Scheele, Clifton & Russell-Building Loan, 1946; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 106)
    - Misc Mortgage Loans A-Z, 1946; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 107)
    - Misc. Real Estate Records, 1946; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 108)
    - Horn, Betsy B.: 1525 14th St., 1947; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 109)
    - Protestant Episcopal Cathedral Foundation-Notes, 1947; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 110)
    - Wood, Jas. & Ruth-5126 15th St. (Arlington, VA), 1947; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 111)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans, 1947; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 112)
    - Misc Real Estate Records, 1947; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 113)
    - Brooks, Thos. R.-3927 Oliver St., 1948; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 114)
    - Danisch, John A.-7115 Moorland Lane (Bethesda, MD), 1948; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 115)
    - Garlock, Roger B.-6216 Green Tree Rd. (Bethesda, MD), 1948; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 116)
    - Mitchell, Edward A.-1603 35th St., 1948; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 117)
    - Protestant Episcopal Cathedral Foundation-Notes, 1948; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 118)
    - Sadd, Victor-1642 Connecticut Ave., 1948; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 119)
    - Washington Wholesale Drug Exchange, 1948; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 120)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans A-Z, 1948; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 121)
    - Misc. Real Estate Records, 1948; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 122)
    - Baker, Lewis S.-5512 30th Place, 1949; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 123)
    - Crump, Edmund H.-3815 "S" St., 1949; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 124)
    - Evans, Chas. T-4511 Amherst Lane (Bethesda, MD), 1949; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 125)
    - Fadeley, Chas. R.-3820 Jocelyn St., 1949; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 126)
    - Foster, Raymond C.-508 Fern Place, 1949; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 127)
    - Leitch, Pauline-4812 43rd Place, 1949; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 128)
    - Lloyd, Jesse W.-5304 26th Ave., 1949; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 129)
    - Mitchell, Edward A.-1603 35th St., 1949; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 130)
    - Protestant Episcopal Cathedral Foundation-Notes, 1949; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 131)
    - Pusateri, Frank P.-4431 46th St., 1949; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 132)
    - Sadd, Victor-1642 Connecticut Ave., 1949; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 133)
    - Misc. Real Estate Records, 1949; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 134)
    - Burka, Fred-2901 Brandywine St., 1950; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 135)
    - Dierkorn, Henry K.-7206 Bradley Blvd. (Bethesda, MD), 1950; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 136)
    - Foster, Raymond C.-508 Fern Place, 1950; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 137)
    - Kerry, Richard J.-3806 Jenifer St., 1950; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - Malloy, John-4925 Washington Place, 1950; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 139)
    - Murray, Richard R.-943 26th St. (Arlington, VA), 1950; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 140)
    - Packer, Earl-3013 "Q" St., 1950; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 141)
    - Pell, Claiborne-1421 33rd St., 1950; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 142)
    - Protestant Episcopal Cathedral Foundation-Notes, 1950; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 143)
    - Shaw, Edwin B.-11 Magnolia Pkway (Chevy Chase, MD), 1950; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 144)
    - Weismuller, John-1443 Fairmont St., 1950; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 145)
    - Witman, Wm.-1529 33rd St., 1950; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 146)
    - Woodward, Stanley-3009 "N" Street, 1950; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 147)
    - Young, R.D.-2220 "R" St., 1950; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 148)
    - Misc Real Estate Records, 1950; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 149)
    - Altland, Paul D.-8519 Parkhill Dr. (Bethesda, MD), 1951; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 150)
    - Brooks, Thos. R.-3927 Oliver St. 1951-72, Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 151)
    - Callahan, Daniel J.-Farm in Poolesville, MD 1951-60, Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 152)
    - Callahan, Daniel J. Cont. 1963-69, 1951; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 153)
    - Carlson, Raymond A.-4843 Leland St. (Bethesda, MD) 1951-1963, Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 154)
    - Coleman, Horace-4505 Saul Rd. (Kensington, MD) 1951-68, Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 155)
    - Dierkorn, Henry K.-7206 Bradley Blvd., 1951; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 156)
    - Donhauser, Robert-3 Hesketh St. (Chevy Chase, MD), 1951; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 157)
    - Fadeley, Chas. R.-3820 Jocelyn St. 1951-59, Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 158)
    - Hall, Fontaine-6004 Poindexter Rd. (Lux Manor, MD) 1951-64, Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 159)
    - Harper, Brig. Gen'l Rob't H.-Various Properties 1951-64, Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 160)
    - MacMurray, Rose-Fairfax County, VA, 1951; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 161)
    - Mitchell, Edward A.-1603 35th St. 1951-1960, Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 162)
    - Sterrett, Wm. D.-3507 Springland Lane 1951-64, Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 163)
    - Work, Burel-9917 Woodburn Rd. (Silver Spring, MD), 1951; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 164)
    - Yalom, Abraham-9th & Varnum St., 1951; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 165)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans A-Z, 1951; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 166)
    - Real Estate Credit - Regulation X, 1951; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Misc. Real Estate Records, 1951; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Hoover, Thos. N. - Belle Haven (Fairfax Co., VA.), 1952; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Jalanora, Julian - Various Properties, 1952-1969; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Leithch, Pauline - 4812 43rd Pl., 1952-1955; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Minott, Jos. A. - 1623 35th St, 1952; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Real Estate Credit - Regulation X, 1952; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Misc. Real Estate Records, 1952; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Bryarlyn, WM. A. - 8907 Melwood Rd (Bethesda, Ma), 1953-1954; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Church, Frederick L. - Arlington Forest, VA., 1953-1963; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - DeMaudit, Priscilla - 3503 Fulton St., 1953; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Merkle, Kathleen - Assumed Loan of Chas. H. Tompkins, 1953-1962; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Pendleton, L. Battaille - 8819 Kensington Pkwy (Chevy Chase, Md), 1953-1961; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Porter, Stephen O. - 6930 Greenvale ST., 1953-1963; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Shaw, Edwin B. - 11 Magnolia Pkwy, 1953-1964; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Thayer, Mary - 2719 Dumbarton Ave, 1953-1954; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans, A - Z, 1953; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Barnard, John L. - 3235 "R" St., 1954; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Connolly, Neville K. - 4010 Reno Rd, 1954-1964; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Dierkoph, Henry K. - 5722 Bradley Blvd., 1954-1964; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Ikenberry, Henry C. - 3917 Oliver St. (Chevy Chase, MD.), 1954-1967; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Mills, Lorraine W. - Woodlawn Manor (Fairfax, VA.), 1954; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Morgan, Norman D. - 106 West Myrtle St. (Alexandria, VA.), 1954-1960; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Poole, Robert M. - Huntington Terrace (Montg. Co. Md.), 1954; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Short, Stannard - Salona Village (Fairfax, VA.), 1954-1964; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Thayer, Philip W. - 1400 29th St., 1954-1966; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans, A - Z, 1954; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Antonelli, Dominic F. - High Point (Montg. Co., MD.), 1955-1967; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Bumstead, Geo. - "Edgemoor" (Montg. Co. MD), 1955-1970; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Cardenter, Donald M. - Elmwood Estates (Fairfax, VA), 1955-1957; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Davey, Kenneth W. - Mt. Vernon District Land, 1955; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Doyle, Rob't E. - 3531 Woodbine St. (Chevy Chase, MD.), 1955-1960; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Fowler, Donald - 3307 Alabama Ave. (Alexandria, VA.), 1955-1970; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - McCammon, Jos. - 4347 Forest Lane, 1955-1966; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Murray, Geo. K. - 5100 Mahant St. (Mont. Co., MD), 1955; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Sargeant, Howland H. - 2804 "N" St., 1955-1963; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Shroyer, Louis W. - 5107 Nahant St. (Mont. Co., MD), 1955-1970; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Tapely, Jas. L. - 707 Beechwood Dr. (Chevy Chase, MD), 1955; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Woodward, Stanley - 3009 "n" st, 1955-1963; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Yereance, Alexander W. - 3905 N. Udland St. (Arlington, VA), 1955-1959; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans, A - Z, 1955; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Chaszar, Edward - 3 Accotink Rd (Fairfax Co. VA), 1956-1967; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - DeLashmutt, Katherine S. - 1316 12th St, 1956-1963; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Ellis, Elizabeth - 1350 Nicholson St, 1956; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Harr, Edith May - 901 "H" St., 1956-1966; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Henderson, Herbert T. - 9509 Clement Rd. (Silver Spring, MD), 1956-1961; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Ketchum, Barcara B. - 3669 Upton St, 1956; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Minte, Rob't E. - Fairfax Rd. (Fairfax Co., VA), 1956-1963; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Paul, Norman S. - 1308 29th St, 1956 -1958; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Randolph, Oscar De Wolf - 3030 44th St., 1956; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Sweetser, Wilmer T. - 5510 Edson Lane (Rockville, MD), 1956-1962; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Worthington, Geo. Y. - Westgate (Montg. Co., MD.), 1956-1965; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans, A - Z, 1956; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Avis, Dwight E. - 1526 Locust Rd., 1957; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Fillion, John A. - 3805 E. Thornapple St. (Chevy Chase, MD), 1957; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Levy, Harold R. - 1529 33rd St., 1957; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Lucker, Rob't P. - 2900 "P" St., 1957-1959; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Mohler, J. Rupert - 1142 and 1144 19th St., 1957-1962; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Stevens, Wm. Moor - 821 Timber Branch Pkwy (Alex., VA,), 1957; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans, A - Z, 1957; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Carr, Roland T. - 3806 Gramercy St. 1958 - 1969, Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Collier, Teunis F. - 3039 Dent Place, 1958-1964; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Gray, Wm. C. - 1324 34th St., 1958; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Kendall, Marjorie R. - 912-14 19th St., 1958-1963; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Smith, Mark O. - 5211 Locust Ave (Bethesda, Md.), 1958-1966; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Thompson, Nina C. - 4438 "Q" St., 1958; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Woodward, Stanley - 3003 "N" st, 1958-1962; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Worthington, Geo. Y. - Construction Co. - 3053 "Q" st, 1958; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans, A - Z, 1958; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Baker, Lewis S. - 5512 30th Place, 1959; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - Crump, Edmund H. - 6212 Green Tree Rd (Bethesda, MD), 1959-1968; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - Drogaris, Peter A. - 5906 Roosevelt St. (Bradley Hills, MD), 1959; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - Enders, Thos. O. - 1318-20 20th St., 1959; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - Kauffman, John M. - 3417 R St., 1959; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Moore, Jos. W. - 1762 "T" St., 1959; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Rones, Benjamin - 3131 "N" St., 1959; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - Stiefel, Nathan Et Al (Howard Theatre Co.) - 622 "T" St, 1959; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - Sullivan, May M. - 1417 "U" St., 1959; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - Wood, Jas. - 5126 15th St., 1959; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Associated Fi ve, Inc. - 3308 "R" St., 1960; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - Burka, Fred - 2901 Brandywine St, 1960-1963; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - Burson, Hazel T. - 3320 Dent Place, 1960; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Kelly, John E. - 6715 Cemalier Dr. (Chevy Chase, MD.), 1960-1965; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - Leiter, Marian - 3259 "R" St., 1960-1969; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Mac Murray, Frank G. - 2224 Decatur Place, Undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Meloy, Francis E. - 2909 "P" St., 1960; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Trammell, Edgar R. - 3108 "M" St., 1960; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - Bierbower, Jas. J. - 41 "D" St., 1961; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - Bradbury, Howard - 1608 Crittenden St, 1961; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 89)
    - Edwards, Malcolm A. - Great Falls, VA., 1961-1964; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 90)
    - Enders, Thos. O. - 1318-20 29th St., 1961-1966; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - Linkins, Mable Kent - 734-40 9th St., 1961-1971; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - Rivello, Nino J. - 7139 Georgia Ave, 1961-1968; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - Stephenson, Bennie Y. - 409 Constitution Ave, 1961; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans, 1961; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - Cable, Malcolm W. - 400 S. Pitt St. (Alex., VA.), 1962; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - Coleman, Howard S. - 5919 Espey Lane (McLean, VA.), 1962-1964; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Maisti, Louis A. - 9200 Limestone Pl. (College Park, MD), 1962-1970; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - Sipe, John H. - 2428 N. Florida St. (Arlington, VA.), 1962-1966; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 99)